Guide to the Laboratory for Elementary Particle Physics photographs, 1950-2005.
Laboratory for Elementary Particle Physics photographs
- Various material (Box 11-18)
  - VS-6871-1-32 Early 10-GeV operations (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - VS-6891-1 Wilson Lab, Horse paddock, horse rider (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - VS-6892-1,2 Boyce McDaniel, Tunnel (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Old Apparatus and Personnel of Newman Lab:, 1948-07-20, 1948-09-18, 1949-07-18, 1949-10-22, 1950-03-24 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - “A Visit to CESR and CLEO” (Box 18)
  - CLEO, Primarily DR II, C. Bebek, D. Peterson, DR stringers (Box 18)
  - CESR, Primarily Components, Boyce McDaniel in Tunnel (Box 18)
  - CHESS (Box 18)
  - 140-Ken Wilson Portrait (Box 18)
  - 040-C-BUG Helium Balloon being filled (Box 18)
  - 080-CLEO II Magnet Coil Oxford Drawing (Box 18)
  - 066-SRF cavities: 1-cell, 3-cell, 5-cell, subassemblies (Box 18)
  - LEPP Negatives (Box 19)
  - Photos-Ground breaking for Newman Lab; Model of synchroton and first beam; various other photos including one of Robert Wilson, 1947-1948 (Box 19)
  - Photos- Semi-automotic wire stringing machine and prototypes used in CLEO II particle detector and plated wire in draft chamber of CLEO II (Box 19)
  - Polaroid slides used for teaching-samples (Box 19)
  - Sol Goldberg photos on mat boards: #6871, nos. 2-5, 8-13, 17-22, 25, 26, 29- various frames (Box 20)
  - 063 folder containing slides, photos and negatives (Box 20)
- photo albums, see Box 14 for index.
  - 50 10-GeV (Building Construction) (Box 21)
  - 51 10-GeV (Tunnel Construction) (Box 22)
  - 52 10-GeV (Linac) (Box 22)
  - 54 10-GeV (Electronics) (Box 22)
  - 60 CESR (Building Construction) (Box 22)
  - 62-CESR (Magnets) (Box 22)
  - 63 CESR (Injection) (Box 22)
  - 64 CESR (Vacuum) (Box 23)
  - 65 CESR (RF) (Box 23)
  - 66 CESR (Superconducting RF) (Box 23)
  - 66 CESR (Superconducting RF) (Box 24)
  - 66 CESR (Superconducting RF) (Box 25)
  - 67 CESR (Miscellaneous) (Box 25)
  - 70 CLEO I (Mechanical) (Box 25)
  - 80 CLEO II (Mechanical) (Box 25)
  - 80 CLEO II (Mechanical) (Box 26)
  - 80 CLEO II (Mechanical) (Box 27)
  - 81 CLEO II (Electronics) (Box 27)
  - 82 CLEO III (Mechanical) (Box 27)
  - 82 CLEO III (Mechanical) (Box 28)
  - 83 CLEO III (Electronics) (Box 28)
  - 90 Mini-Beta (Box 28)
  - 110 CHESS (Box 28)
  - 120 CUSB (Box 28)
  - 130 Achievements (Box 28)
  - 131 Symposiums, Conferences, Meeting, etc. (Box 28)
  - 131 Symposiums, Conferences, Meeting, etc. (Box 29)
  - 132 Education / Outreach (Box 29)
  - 140 Personnel (Box 29)
  - 150 Social Functions (Box 29)
  - 150 Social Functions (Box 30)
  - 150 Social Functions (Box 31)
  - 150 Social Functions (Box 32)
  - 160 Miscellaneous / General (Box 32)
  - 161 General Physics (Box 32)
  - 162 Public Relations (Box 32)
  - Overhead Transparencies (Box 33)
  - Large Negatives (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 33)
  - Photos 6533-10017 (Box 34)
  - Photos 10282-10677 (Box 34)
  - Photos 10678-12388 (Box 34)
  - Photos 12480-12595 (Box 34)
  - Photos 12596-12805 (Box 34)
  - Photos 12805-12873 (Box 34)
  - Photos 13232-13314 (Box 34)
  - Photos 13321 (Box 34)
  - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 34)
  - Slides - CLEO, CESR (Box 34)
  - Slides, 1965-1989 (Box 35)
- Oversized items (Mapcase-folder O/S)